Cell: 909-348-4459

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/alee046 Portfolio Site: www.anthonylee.xyz

20811 Canon Ridge Lane Walnut, CA 91789

alee9011@gmail.com

Skills

Javascript, jQuery, CSS, HTML5, Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Angular, MongoDB, Express, Node, js, Bootstrap & Sass, PostgreSQL, Socket.io, Ionic Framework, PHP, MySQL, Magento

Projects

Coordinet: Location-sharing based chat-app that allows users to communicate on their phones through a combination of custom Google map markers and local chatrooms. Technologies used: Ionic, Socket.io, Node, js, HTML5, Javascript, jQuery, Animate.css

ConShareto: Worked as a team to develop a concert-tracking application with an easy to use UI using the MEN stack. My focus was in utilizing API calls (Jambase) to pull out concert information and developing the user-interface of the application. Technologies used: Node.js, MongoDB, Express, HTML5, Javascript, jQuery

Product Guide/Quiz - (Better Life Products): The product guide is an inhouse-app that provided new salespeople an accessible and tracklable method to learn about the products that we carry. Features include: a pdf generator that pulls information from a MySQL database and a customziable quiz-application.

Technologies Used: PHP, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Magento, mySQL

Hold'em: A Texas Hold-em simulator I built after my second week at General Assembly. Technologies used: HTML5, CSS, Javascript, jQuery

Employment History

Better Life Products, Inc, Torrance,CA Web Developer (LAMP)

2016 - 2016

- Converted PSDst to responsive web pages/ Developed front/back-end Magento features
- Developed the product guide, which is an in-house training program for the new hirees.
- Conceptualized and implemented a new project management workflow.

General Assembly, Los Angeles, California **Web Development Immersive Student**

2015 - 2015

• GA's WDI is a 12 week immersive web development program, during this course I spent 600 + hours learning computer science topics and how to build web applications.

Lih-Jen International Elementary School, Taipei, Taiwan **Homeroom Teacher**

2014 - 2015

Education

BA, Political Science

2013

University of California, Riverside, Riverside, CA